ASANTE GIDEON

Email: mordecai361@gmail.com

Contact: 0243860216

PERSONAL DETAILS

Sex: Male Residential address: Buduburam-Kasoa

Date of birth: 1st May, 1994 Hometown: Akim Oda - Eastern Region

Marital Status: Single Emergency contact: 0244446092 Nationality: Ghanaian (Kwame Boakye)

CAREER OBJECTIVE

With passion for computing, I would like to utilize my skills and experience as well as passion for computing, exploring, teaching and research. Moreover, I would like to work with other professionals to improve my skills and help the organization to fully achieve its set goals and targets as I grow with the organization.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

University for Development Studies, Tamale- Northern Region, 2014 -2018

BSc. Computing with Accounting

St. Michael's Senior High School, Akoasi – Eastern Region, 2009 - 2013

W.A.S.S.C.E (Agricultural Science)

Pankese Roman Catholic School, Eastern Region, 2006 - 2009

B.E.C.E

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Adam Family Clinic, Account Person, South Odorkor, Nov., 2020 – April, 2021.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- · In charge of the day to account work within the facility.
- · Managing data, files or receipts and processes.
- · In charge of all financial records and taking monies to bank.

Adventist Preparatory School, Head Teacher (Voluntary Service), Asante Akim Agogo, January – September, 2020.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- · In charge of the day to day running of the school.
- · Managing people, data, and processes.
- · Improving school leadership
- · Cultivating leadership in others

Collins Senior High School, ICT Teacher (Voluntary Service), Asante Akim Agogo, 2019

RESPONSIBILITY

· Teaching form 3 class elective ICT

Non-Formal Education Office, Facilitator (National Service), Asante Akim Agogo, 2018 - 2019

RESPONSIBILITY

· Serving as a class or module facilitator

St. Gregory Catholic Hospital, Medical Records Unit (Industrial Attachment) Gomoa Buduburam, May – July 2017

RESPONSIBILITY

· In charge of keeping medical records of patients and retrieving those records when needed.

Community Field Practical Program (Third Trimester Field Practical Program [TTFPP]) In the Nakpachei Community (Yendi Municipal), 2015 -2016

RESPONSIBILITIES

- · Collection and analysis of data
- · Writing community reports
- · Writing community proposals for sponsorships

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Ghana National Association of Adventist Students, North Ghana Zonal President,
 2017 2018
- Ghana National Association of Adventist Students, UDS Navrongo Chapter President, 2017 - 2018
- Ghana National Association of Adventist Students, UDS Navrongo Chapter Youth Leader, 16th -18th September, 2017

SEMINARS ATTENDED

- Web Development Bootcamp, Udemy
- Human Resource Seminar, October 2017
- Web Development Seminar, December 2017
- Leadership Seminar, September 2017

LANGUAGES SPOKEN

- English, Spoken (Excellent), Written (Excellent)
- Twi, Spoken (Excellent), Written (Excellent)

SKILLS/COMPETENCIES

- Influential person
- Good presentation skills
- Good communication skills
- Able to learn new skills efficiently and apply them when needed
- Fluent in the use of the Microsoft Office Suite
- Good programming skills (Software and Web Development [Frontend & Backend])
- Internet skills
- Operating system installations
- Teaching

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Researching
- Innovation
- Programming

- Watching documentaries
- Learning new I.T stuffs
- Teaching

REFEREES

Mr. Opoku-Ware Yeboah

Nestle Ghana Limited

Human Resource and Payroll Admin.

Tema – Ghana

0501323722

yeboah.opoku-ware@gh.nestle.com

Mr. Edward Attah-Asamoah

Non-Formal Education Office

District Coordinator

Asante Akim Agogo

0245090074

Dr. Alhassan Abdul-Barik

University for Development Studies

Lecturer,

Department of Computer Science,

Navrongo Campus.

0246388160